{
    "subject": "resource/Johnny_Maestro_&_the_Brooklyn_Bridge",
    "predicate": "ontology/hometown",
    "object": "resource/United_States",
    "human_readable": "Johnny Maestro & the Brooklyn Bridge was born in United States.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9598639607429504,
            "question": "Where was Johnny Maestro & the Brooklyn Bridge born?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7407532930374146,
            "question": "Is Johnny Maestro & the Brooklyn Bridge an American band?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7022433876991272,
            "question": "Who were some of the members of Johnny Maestro & the Brooklyn Bridge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6874819993972778,
            "question": "When was Johnny Maestro & the Brooklyn Bridge formed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6553308963775635,
            "question": "What country is Johnny Maestro & the Brooklyn Bridge from?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5908156037330627,
            "question": "What is the legacy of Johnny Maestro & the Brooklyn Bridge?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.4762760400772095,
            "question": "Did Johnny Maestro & the Brooklyn Bridge tour internationally?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.32121652364730835,
            "question": "Has Johnny Maestro & the Brooklyn Bridge won any awards?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3133000433444977,
            "question": "What genre of music is Johnny Maestro & the Brooklyn Bridge known for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.22102700173854828,
            "question": "What are some of Johnny Maestro & the Brooklyn Bridge's most popular songs?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Johnny Maestro & the Brooklyn Bridge was born in United States.",
            "html": "dbpedia_9285_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What genre of music is Johnny Maestro & the Brooklyn Bridge known for?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9285_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Has Johnny Maestro & the Brooklyn Bridge won any awards?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9285_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Did Johnny Maestro & the Brooklyn Bridge tour internationally?",
            "html": "dbpedia_9285_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9285_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9285_19.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9285_27.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9285_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9285_4.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9285_46.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9285_55.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9285_56.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9285_60.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_9285_7.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'no'}\n```\n\nExplanation: The provided documents do not contain any information about Johnny Maestro's place of birth. While it mentions he is from New York City and Manhattan, it does not specify that he was born in the United States. Therefore, we cannot confirm this statement based on the given context."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Most Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "qwen2.5": {
            "reason": "Johnny Maestro was born in the lower East side of Manhattan, New York City, United States, not in Brooklyn or any other specific group name.",
            "category": 2
        }
    }
}